-刚才怎么了 -没什么
-What was that? -Nothing.
-给我点小提示就好 -不 不能给提示
-Okay, just give me one little hint. -No. No hints.
我们快到了
We're almost there.
我要拿掉了
Okay, I'm going to take this off.
不不不 你说喜欢惊喜的
No, no, no. Hey, you said you like surprises.
是 没错 但我总得知道是什么
Yeah, I do. When I know what they are.
你会很爱的
You're going to love it.
我保证
Promise.
是啊 我爱这风景
Yeah. I already love the view.
我们到了
All right. Here we are.
小心脚步
Watch your step. Watch your step.
我看不见
I can't see.
好 往前 停住
Okay. Move forward. Stop.
可以拿下来了
Now taking it off.
就是现在
Now.
真的假的?
Are you kidding?
怎么会 我都不知道这里开幕了
How? I... I... I didn't even know this place was open yet.
我托人把我们列入开幕夜名单
I pulled some favors and I got us on the list for opening night.
你确定我穿这样可以?
Are you sure I'm dressed all right?
你看起来美极了
You look like a million bucks.
来吧
Come on.
嘿
Hey!
别偷喷泉里的硬币
Don't steal coins from the fountain.
会带来厄运
It's bad luck.
-抱歉 先生 -去吧
-Sorry, sir. -Go on.
微笑
Smile.
-您的票 -谢谢
-Here's your ticket. -Thank you.
-您好 想要拍照吗 -谢谢
-Hello, sir. Would you like a photo? -Thank you.
大家注意脚步
Watch your step, everyone.
要进来吗
You coming?
我们坐下一班
We'll take the next one.
来吧 挤得下
Ah, come on. We can fit you in.
谢谢
Thanks.
上楼
Going up.
请见谅
Oh, excuse me.
抱歉 有时会这样
Sorry. It does that sometimes.
（最大容量1300磅或8名成人）
关于天景塔的冷知识
Some fun facts about the Sky View Tower.
高494英尺 9,000多吨重
It's 494 feet tall and weighs over 9,000 tons.
由钢铁 钢筋混凝土和玻璃盖成
It's made of steel and reinforced concrete and glass.
更厉害的是整个计划
And even more impressive, the entire project
比预期提前五个月完成
was completed five months ahead of schedule.
这是好事吗
Is that a good thing?
不是盖的吧?
What did I tell you?
-好高级 -您好
-Fancy. -Yes?
需要帮忙吗
May I help you?
我们有订位 坎贝尔
We have a reservation. Campbell.
抱歉 已经满了
Oh, I'm sorry, but we're already over capacity
开幕夜没有空位了
for opening night. We cannot accommodate you.
请让开 感谢
If you wouldn't mind just stepping aside. Thank you so much. It's okay.
其实我跟杰克说了 他在吗 我想找他
I worked it out with Jake. Is he here? I could speak with--
我们今早开除了杰克 感谢
We let Jake go this morning. Thank you so much.
-怎么回事 -等一下
-What's going on? -One second, one second. Um...
先生 我很尊重你 但请你帮帮我
Sir, I know you're a very important man, um, but maybe you could help me out...
拜托了
Please.
你让我很为难 抱歉 我帮不了你
You're tearing me apart. But I'm sorry, I can't help you.
请到旁边
Now, if you wouldn't mind...
富勒先生 欢迎 我们为您准备了好位子
Oh, Mr. Fuller! How nice to see you. We have a lovely table for you.
谢谢 这边请
Thank you. This way, please.
-我们去酒吧 -什么
-Let's go to the bar. -What?
表现自然点
Just act natural.
看看这景观
Wow. Look at that view.
怎么了
What?
糗大了
Oh, no.
你怕高
You're scared of heights.
什么 没事 我只是…
What? Oh, no. I'm just...
我没来过这么高的地方
I've just never been this high up before.
对不起 今晚老是出丑 我多希望一切完美
I'm so sorry. This night's turning into such a disaster. I really wanted it to be perfect.
嘿
Hey.
够完美了
It is perfect.
因为我跟你在一起
Because I'm with you.
你还好吗
You okay?
-死不了 -是吗
-I think I'll live. -Yeah?
你看 免费香槟
Hey, look, free champagne.
我最爱的酒
That's my favorite kind.
随即奉上
Coming right up.
-好了 -我马上回来
-Okay. -I'll be right back.
请问洗手间在哪
Excuse me. Where's the ladies' room?
舞池的另一边
Other side of the dance floor.
谢谢 马上回来
Thank you. We'll be right back.
嗨 宝贝
Hi, sweetie.
都还好吗
Is everything all right?
我很好 谢谢
I'm fine. Thank you.
你怀孕多久了
How far along are you?
什么
What?
我没有…
No. I'm not...
我不确定 也许一两个月
I don't know, exactly. Maybe one or two months.
真是好消息
That's wonderful news.
是吗
Isn't it?
我还没告诉我男朋友
I haven't told my boyfriend yet.
他爱你吗
Does he love you?
是的
Yes.
那他就不会放手
Then he won't let go.
-谢谢 -不客气
-Thank you. -Of course.
再见
Bye.
好 快结束了
Okay. It's almost over.
好
Okay.
找到你了
There you are.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
还好
Yeah.
应该吧
I think so.
来吧
Come on.
去透透气
Let's get some fresh air.
-我真的需要… -我想…
-I really need---I wanted to--
你先说
Uh... you go first.
好吧
Okay.
我本来想在晚餐时说 但这里太美了
-I was going to do this at dinner, but seeing as we have this view...
嘿
Hey!
别丢硬币 会害死人
Don't throw that penny. It could kill somebody.
抱歉 没问题
Oh, I'm so sorry. Of course. Yeah.
死胖子
Fat ass.
过去几年...
Um, these past few years...
真是太神奇了
have been absolutely magical.
因为有你
And that's, uh... that's because of you.
爱莉丝 我想跟你共度一生
Iris, I want to spend the rest of my life with you.
你是说跟我们...?
You mean... with us?
什么
What?
对不起
Sorry.
我…
I...
我是全世界最幸运的男人
I'm the luckiest guy in the world.
难道你不心烦
What? You're not upset?
开玩笑 才不 这太棒了
Are you kidding me? No, this... this is... This is incredible.
-真的 -我们要组个家庭了
-Really? -We're going to start a family.
那你愿意吗
Um... so... will you?
愿意
Oh, uh... Yes.
-会不会太紧 -刚刚好
-Is it too tight? -Uh... it's perfect.
我们去庆祝吧
Hey. Let's go celebrate.
♪ 你就是会让我想喊叫 踢起脚跟 喊叫 ♪
♪ 举起双手 喊叫 挥动双手 喊叫 ♪
♪ 来吧 喊叫 别忘了说你愿意 ♪
♪ 别忘了说 耶耶耶 ♪
♪ 说你愿意 ♪
♪ 当下就说 小宝贝 ♪
♪ 来吧 来吧 ♪
♪ 说你愿意 ♪
♪ -说出来 -说你愿意 ♪
♪ 来吧 ♪
♪ 快说吧 快说吧 ♪
♪ 快说吧 ♪
♪ 你就是会让我想喊叫 ♪
♪ -抬起脚跟 喊叫 -喊叫 ♪
♪ 挥动双手 ♪
♪ 喊叫 ♪
♪ 轻松一下 喊叫 轻松一下 喊叫 ♪
♪ 大声一点 喊叫 大声一点 喊叫 ♪
♪ -嘿嘿嘿 -嘿嘿嘿 ♪
♪ 跳起喊叫 跳起喊叫 ♪
♪ 大家喊叫 跳起喊叫 ♪
♪ 大家喊叫 喊叫喊叫 ♪
♪ 喊叫喊叫 喊叫喊叫 ♪
♪ 雨滴不断打在我头上 ♪
♪ 但这不代表我的眼眶就会泛红 ♪
抓住我的手 上来
Paul! Grab my hand! Pull up!
撑住
Hold on!
退后
No! Stay back!
-退后 -等等 救命
-No, stay back! -Wait! Help!
保罗 抓住我的手
Paul! Grab my hand!
不要
No!
不
大家快下楼
Everyone down the stairs!
让开 小孩先走
Out of my way Children first!
排成一列
Single file!
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
去搭电梯
To the elevator!
女士 请借过 我要操作
Excuse me, ma'am. Please. I need to get to the controls.
走开
Move!
-让我进去 -先生 请退后
-Let me in. -Please, sir. Step back!
已经超载了
We're already over capacity!
少来了 走开
I swear to God, move!
让我进去
Let me in!
救命 拜托
Help, please! Please!
抓住我
Grab on!
抓住
救命
Help!
过来
Come here.
唉呀
Well,
我能理解向量乘法很可怕 但反应太大了吧
I realize vector multiplication is scary, but it's not that scary.
好了 今天到此为止
All right, that's it for today.
下周开始准备期末
We'll start prepping for the final next week.
雷耶斯小姐
Ms. Reyes.
我们需要谈谈
We need to talk.
好
Yeah.
我们要组个家庭了
We're going to start a family.
别丢硬币 会害死人
Don't throw that penny. It could kill somebody.
大家快下楼
Everyone down the stairs!
这个梦会毁了我的人生
Oh, this dream is ruining my life.
我的人生也毁了
Mine, too.
每天晚上 史黛 我根本不能睡
Every night, Stef. God, I'm not getting any sleep.
该死 对不起
Shit, I'm sorry.
能跟你说一件事吗
Um, can I tell you something?
好 说吧
Yeah, what's up?
我梦里的女人叫爱莉丝 对吧
So, the woman in my dream. Her name is Iris, right?
嗯
Okay.
那是我外婆的名字
That was my grandmother's name.
我好像梦到她了
I think I'm dreaming about her.
你认真的吗
Are you serious?
对 问题是我没见过她
Yeah. The thing is, I never even met her.
说不定她都死了
I don't even know if she's alive.
好吧
Okay, well...
那你回家找出外婆 停止这个恶梦
either go home and find out about Grandma and hope that stops the dreams.
不然就留下来死在梦里
Or stay here and die in your sleep for real.
因为我会杀了你
Because I will murder you.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
-好吧 -爱你
-Yeah, yeah, okay. -Love you.
我也爱你
Yeah. Love you, too.
-回家吧 -好
-Go home. -Yeah.
慢走不送
Quietly.
好了
Okay.
-回来了 -嗨 爸
-Hey, there she is! -Hey, Dad.
欢迎回家 女儿 很高兴你回来了
Welcome home, sweetie. So glad you're here.
-我也很高兴 -我好想你
-Yeah, me, too. -I missed you so much.
一定要的
I know.
见到你真好
Oh, so great to see you.
-谢谢 -我帮你拿
-Thank you, thank you. -Let me take that for you.
抱歉 查理暂时睡你房间 我的档案在他房间
Hey, sorry. Charlie took your room a while ago, and my files are in his room,
我帮你铺好沙发床 好吗
so I made up the pullout for you. Is that okay?
好 听起来没问题
Yeah, yeah. No, that sounds totally fine.
那盒妈的旧东西还在吗
Uh, hey, do we still have that box of Mom's old stuff?
里面有照片 还有通讯录
It had, uh, some photos, like an address book
上面有电话号码
with phone numbers in it.
你为什么需要
Uh, why do you want that?
没什么 我记得放在家里
Oh, it's not a big deal. I just thought I saw it lying around here somewhere.
史黛芬妮 怎么了
Stefani, what's going on?
好 这听起来会超怪
Okay, this is going to sound really, really weird,
但我要找到外婆 爱莉丝
but I, uh... I just need to find Mom's mom, Iris.
好 确实很怪
Uh... okay. Yeah, that is weird.
几年前你妈离家后 我就把那些箱子丢了
And, you know, I got rid of those boxes years ago, after your mom left.
嗨 查理
Oh, hi, Charlie.
嗨
Hey.
"嗨 史黛 你好吗 很高兴见到你"
Um, "Hi, Stef. How are you? It's so nice to see you."
随便
Yeah, sure.
我要去表哥家
Uh, I'm going to the cousins.
现在 你姐才刚到家 我们能…
Now? Look, your sister just got home. I thought we...
-我有约了 -这样吧 我载你去
-Well, I had plans. -Actually, you know what? I can drive you.
-反正我也想见他们 -不用啦
-I was wanting to see them anyways. -It's fine.
去见亲戚时 拜托别跟霍华德舅舅提到爱莉丝
Hey. If you're going to see your cousins, please don't talk about Iris to Uncle Howard.
好 没问题
Yeah. Yeah, no problem.
走了
All right.
-拜拜 爱你 -我也爱你
-Bye. Love you. -Love you, too.
查理?
Charlie?
查理 拿掉耳机啦
Charlie... Can you just...
-史黛 -我在跟你说话 你有什么毛病
-Ow. Stef! -...take these out, please? I'm trying to talk to you. What's your problem?
干嘛
What?
你一直不说话
You haven't said anything this entire time.
史黛 你回来干嘛
Stef, why are you here?
你只有过节才会回家
I mean, you only come home for holidays.
好 我有件事告诉你
Okay, I have to tell you something.
但你要保证不会告诉爸
But you have to promise not to tell Dad.
你怀孕了?
What, are you pregnant?
不是 我没怀孕 查理
No, I'm not pregnant, Charlie.
-我不知道 -你怎么会…
-I don't know. -Why would you even...
又没什么 你上大学了
That's not... I mean, you're in college.
你能答应不会告诉爸吗
Okay, can you just promise me you won't tell Dad?
-我为什么要告诉爸 -说真的 查理
-Why would I tell Dad? -It's serious, Charlie.
好啦
All right.
好
Okay.
我被留校察看
I am on academic probation.
怎样啦 查理 别笑了 如果成绩没提高…
What? Charlie, stop laughing! If I don't get my grades up...
我太吃惊了 但挺好笑的
It's kind of a big moment for me.
你成绩优异 当班长
Straight A's. You're a class president.
-毕业生代表竟然辍学了 -查理 很难笑
-Miss Valedictorian is failing out of school. -Charlie, it's not funny.
我成绩没起色就会失去奖学金
If I don't get my grades up, I will lose my scholarship.
好惨 抱歉
That blows. Sorry.
怎么回事
What happened?
我睡不着
I mean, I can't sleep.
每次闭上眼睛 我就反复梦到爱莉丝
Every time I close my eyes, I have this same recurring nightmare about Iris.
我们的外婆 好怪
Our grandmother. I don't...
事有蹊跷
I mean, it has to mean something.
不见得
I don't know.
我也梦到怪事
I dream weird things.
我昨晚梦到热狗把我吞掉
I dreamed a hot dog ate me last night.
-什么 -热狗居然在吃我
-What? That is... -Like the hot dog was eating me.
好吧
Okay.
哥 帮个忙
Dude, can you just do something?
-冷静 会找到他的 -动一下就好
-Dude, calm down, all right? We'll find him. -Just move a little bit.
我不能暂停 这是线上对打 少烦
I can't pause, all right? It's an online match. Are you serious?
-我要找下面 -帮我个忙 滚开
-I have to look under this. -Can you do me a kindness? Fuck off.
-记得上次的事件吗 -这有玩家排名
-You remember what happened last time? -It's a ranked match!
-怎么了 -我找不到帕哥
-What's going on? -I can't find Paco.
靠 又来了
Dude, again?
等等 谁是帕哥
Wait, who's Paco?
不会吧 嗨 表姐
No way! Hey, cuz!
天啊 顺便帮忙找找
Oh, my gosh. Hey, can you help us look?
走路时小心脚步
And just watch your feet, where you're stepping.
好啊 但我要先找你爸
Yeah, yeah, sure. I just... I got to talk to your dad first.
你怎么回家了
What the fuck you doing home?
哥 她辍学了
Oh, dude, she's flunking out of school.
-查理 -咱们是同路人
-Charlie. -Hey, welcome to the club.
-艾瑞克 你找了吗 -帕哥不在楼上
-Erik, dude, have you looked anywhere? -Paco's not upstairs!
但楼下来了稀客呢
But look who's down here.
-嗨 茱莉亚 很抱歉 -你还好吗
-Hey, Julia. Oh, my gosh. I'm so sorry... -How you been?
-查理 -茱莉亚
-Charlie! -Jules.
小帅哥来啦 对了 珍妮会去毕业舞会吗
There's my little Romeo. So, wait, how did the promposal with Jenny go?
-她答应了 -天啊 少害羞了
-Dude, she said yes. -Oh, my God. Stop.Okay, wait
谁是珍妮
Who's, uh... Who's Jenny?
他在青少年救生营认识她
Oh, he met her in junior lifeguards.
青少年救生营 查理 我不知道你在做救生员
Junior lifeguards? Charlie, I didn't... I didn't know you were doing junior lifeguards.
-你没跟我说 -那你要穿什么
-You didn't tell me that. -Okay, so what are you going to wear?
我就简单一点
Uh, I'm just going to keep it simple.
黑西装配花俏的领结
You know, black blazer. But with, like, a fun bowtie.
史黛芬妮 我的天啊
Stef! Stefani! Oh, my gosh!
-嗨 亲爱的 -嗨 布兰达舅妈
-Hi, honey. -Hi, Aunt Brenda.
-你会待多久 -不会太久
-How long are you here for? -Uh, not long.
霍华德舅舅在吗
Is Uncle Howard around?
在 他在后面 我去叫他
Yeah. Yeah, he's out back. I'll get him.
霍华德 史黛芬妮来了 进来
Howard! Stefani's here. Come in!
好耶
Great!
你看起来有点累 都还好吗
You look a little tired. Is everything okay?
史黛 你来啦
Stefi! Look at you!
-嗨 -过来抱一下
-Hey! -Come here, come here.
亲爱的 真高兴见到你
Oh, sweetie. Oh, so good to see you.
饿了吗 我正要弄午餐
Hey, are you hungry? I was just about to make some lunch.
不饿 其实我想聊聊你的妈妈爱莉丝
No, actually. I came here because I wanted to talk to you about your mother, Iris.
-你一向对她避而不谈 -没什么好说的
-I know you don't like to talk about her---There's not much to tell.
孩子们 来吃午餐
Hey, kids, come on, lunch!
只是我做恶梦不断梦到她
It's just that I've been having this recurring nightmare about her.
亲爱的 可能只是压力 你该试试褪黑激素
Oh, honey. It's probably just stress. You should try melatonin.
好 但怪的是我梦到一个真实地点
Okay, but the weird thing is I've been dreaming about a real place
在50年前 名为天景的餐厅
from 50 years ago. It was, like, a restaurant called the Sky View.
你们都知道
You know what it is.
爱莉丝告诉你的
Did... did Iris tell you about it?
她说什么 她有说什么吗 也许我能找她谈谈
What did she say? Did she say anything? Maybe if I could talk to her--
找谁谈谈
Talk to who?
史黛梦到爱莉丝外婆
Oh, Stef is dreaming about Grandma Iris.
-疯子外婆 -我以为她死了
-Ooh, Psycho Granny? -I thought she was dead.
我们都当她死了
Well, she's dead to us.
对 史黛 爱莉丝·坎贝尔心理不正常
Yeah, Stefi, Iris Campbell is a very deeply disturbed woman. End of story.
听着 如果我能跟她谈谈 也许就能停止做恶梦
Look, if I could just talk to her, then maybe... maybe I can get these dreams to stop.
史黛 别说了
Stef, just drop it.
我不懂 出了什么坏事吗
I don't get it. What happened that was so bad?
首先 就是她害你妈发神经
For one thing, she's the reason that your mother is so screwed up.
-什么 -听着 我不想再…
-What? -Look, I just don't want to talk
聊这件事了 好吗
about this anymore, okay?
霍华德舅舅 拜托 我只想问清楚
Uncle Howard, please. I just need to know.
听着 史黛
Look, Stefi.
我们老爸过世后...
After our father died...
爱莉丝突然崩溃
Iris just... snapped.
她不让我们上学 把我们锁在家里
She... she wouldn't let us go to school. She locked us inside the house.
她纠结着各种可怕的死法
She obsessed about all the horrific ways we could die.
最后变得很糟 糟到…
And eventually it got so bad, I mean, so bad...
州政府介入把我和你妈从她身边带走
that the State came in and they took your mother and I away from her.
但还没结束 她透过寄养中心找到我们
But it didn't end there. She tracked us all through foster care,
我们小孩出生时 她开始寄来可怕的信
and when the kids were born, she started sending us these horrible letters
全是讣闻和惨不忍睹的尸体照片
that were full of obituaries and these disturbing pictures of dead bodies.
我们得搬家 不让她联络我们
We had to move so she couldn't contact us anymore.
你还留着那些信吗
Do you still have any of those letters, though?
史黛
Stefi...
听我说
Listen to me.
那个女人很病态又危险
That woman is a sick and dangerous person.
为了你的幸福和安全...
And for your well-being and your safety...
离她远一点
stay the hell away from her.
我找到帕哥了
I found Paco!
谢天谢地
Thank God!
他现在一定很想待在客厅
I'm sure he'd love to be in the living room right now.
-他躲在橱柜里 -大家过来吧
-He was in the pantry. -Come on, guys. Let's go.
他是怎么进去的
How did he even get in there?
拜托帮帮我
I need you to help me.
你听到你舅舅的话了 算了啦
You heard your uncle. Just let it go. Just let it go.
你不懂
You don't understand.
我的人生因为这个梦崩溃
My whole life is falling apart because of this dream.
不只这样 我觉得快疯了
And not only that, I feel like... I feel like I'm losing my mind.
拜托 只有你能帮我
Please, you are the only person who can help me.
我让你跟爱莉丝联络 霍华德不会原谅我的
Howard would never forgive me if I put you in touch with Iris.
求你了
Please.
不管怎样
Whatever you do,
别找餐厅柜子底下的抽屉
do not look in the bottom drawer of the dining room cabinet.
（爱莉丝·坎贝尔）
（私有土地  禁止闯入  走开）
嗨
Hi.
我来找爱莉丝·坎贝尔
I'm here to see Iris Campbell.
你没看到牌子吗
Did you not see the signs?
看到了 可是…
Uh... Uh, yeah. Yes, I did, but...
那就滚蛋 禁止访客
Then get the fuck out of here! No visitors.
我是你孙女
I'm your granddaughter.
史黛芬妮
Stefani.
清空口袋 手机 钥匙都拿出来
Empty your pockets. Phone, keys, everything.
我又不危险
I'm not dangerous.
我担心的不是你
It's not you I'm afraid of.
慢慢进来
Come in slowly.
把门关上 动作快
Shut the door. Quick, quick, quick!
别动
Don't move.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
真的是你
It really is you.
你有你妈的影子
I can see your mother in you.
嗨 我是史黛芬妮
Hi. I'm Stefani--
站住 别动
Stop! Stop. Don't move.
听我指示
Not until I tell you.
别想骗我
Trying to trick me, aren't you?
我才不会掉以轻心
Getting me to let my guard down.
好了 来吧
There you go. Come on.
过来 坐下
Come here. Sit.
好
Okay, um...
坐吧
Sit.
行了
That's it.
怎样 达琳好吗
So... how is Darlene?
你妈还好吗
Your mom okay?
我不知道
No. I don't know.
她在我十岁时离家就失联了
She, uh... She left when I was 10, so we don't... we don't see her anymore.
你是读了我的信才来这里吧
But you saw my letters. That's why you're here, right?
不是
No.
我过来其实是因为梦到天景
I'm actually here because I've been dreaming about the Sky View.
-什么 -没错
-What? -Yeah.
这两个月每晚都是相同的梦
Yeah, every single night for the past two months. It's the same dream.
梦里你在约会 但舞池裂开
In it, you're on a date, but then the dance floor breaks,
还有爆炸 然后你…
and there's an explosion and then you--
坠落 死掉
Fall. And die.
对 每个人都死了
Yeah. Yeah, everyone dies.
那不只是你的梦
It wasn't just your dream.
也是我的预感
It was my premonition.
许多年前 在天景...
Years ago, at the Sky View...
我预见了未来
I got a glimpse into the future
看到死神即将下手
and saw what Death was about to do.
我本来想在晚餐时说 但这里太美了
I was going to do this at dinner, but seeing as we have this view...
嘿 别丢硬币 会害死人
Hey! Don't throw that penny. It could kill somebody.
抱歉 没问题
Oh, I'm so sorry. Of course.
死胖子
Fat ass.
过去几年 真是太神奇了
These past few years have been absolutely magical.
因为有你
And that's all because of you.
不行 我…
No, no, no. I...
这样不对 我…
This isn't right. I...
这是拒绝吗
Is that a no?
每个人都会死
Everyone's going to die.
完了 整栋楼会倒塌
No, the whole building is going to come down.
真的吗
Are you serious?
-硬币 -爱莉丝
-The penny. -Iris?
-给我 -搞什么 小姐
-Give me that! -What the hell, lady?
-给我 -你要干嘛
-Give it to me! -What are you doing?
你他妈哪根筋不对
What the fuck is wrong with you?
爱莉丝?
Iris?
♪ 你就是会让我想喊叫 踢起脚跟 喊叫 ♪
借过
Move!
♪ 挥动双手 喊叫 ♪
♪ 来吧 喊叫 别忘了说你愿意 ♪
♪ 别忘了说 耶耶耶 ♪
停止演奏
Stop playing! Stop playing!
大家快离开舞池
Everyone needs to get off the dance floor!
玻璃快碎了
The glass is about to break.
-大家快离开 -女士
-Everyone needs to get off now! -Ma'am.
等等 不要 离开舞池
Wait! No! Get off the dance floor!
-爱莉丝 -你们快离开
-Iris! -You need to get off!
离开
Get off!
那晚我救了很多人
I saved a lot of lives that night.
那些人本来不该被救的
Lives that were never meant to be saved.
后来餐厅就关闭了
They closed the restaurant after that.
说要额外装修
Said it needed additional renovations.
但从此就没再开张
But it never reopened.
最后餐厅就拆了
Eventually they tore it down.
等等 原来你阻止了灾难
Wait, so you stopped the disaster.
对
Yes.
但死神痛恨有人破坏他的计划
But Death doesn't like it when you fuck with his plans.
这些年 他回来杀死那晚在场的人
So, over the years, he came back and he killed everyone who was there that night.
包括我的保罗
Including my Paul.
等一下 你是说死神回来了?
Wait a minute. I'm sorry. Did you... Did you say Death came back?
他杀人不眨眼
He's a relentless son of a bitch.
绝不会善罢干休
Won't stop until he finishes the job.
但我学会察觉他的动静
But I taught myself how to see him coming.
预测他的一举一动
To anticipate his every move.
多年来我一直阻挡他
I've been keeping him at bay for years now.
但他终于逮到我 癌症
But now he's got me. Cancer.
-扯不扯 -很遗憾
-Believe that shit? -Sorry.
两个月前诊断出来
Got the diagnosis two months ago.
等等 我就是那时开始做恶梦
Wait, that's when I started having my dream.
对吧 这是征兆
See? It's a sign.
好 但为什么我会梦见你的预测
Okay, but why am I dreaming about what you saw?
也许癌症把我的预感传到你身上
Maybe my cancer passed my premonition onto you.
也许命运不按牌理出牌 天晓得
Maybe it's fate's demented sense of humor. Who the hell knows?
重点是老天说话时你要注意
What matters is that when the universe speaks, you pay attention.
我看到你了 混蛋
I see you, you fuck.
-你在跟谁说话 -死神
-Who are you talking to? -Death.
他以为你来了让我分心
He thinks I'm distracted because you're here.
我要教会你这本笔记
I have to teach you everything in this book.
打基础急不得 你要留下来
It'll take some time to learn the basics, so you'll need to stay here.
-留下来? -外面世界太危险了
-Stay here? -The outside world is too dangerous.
我20年没出去 这里很安全
I haven't stepped out there in 20 years. In here, we can be safe.
看到没?
See that?
是啊
Yeah.
这些都是我的研究
This is all my research.
我毕生的心血
My life's work.
抱歉 我不能留下来
Look, I'm... I'm sorry. I can't... I can't stay here.
我要回学校 但我会回来找你
I... I have to get back to school, but, you know, I'll come back and I'll visit.
别走 我生病活不久了 你不能离开
No, I'm sick! I won't be alive that long. You can't leave.
你不懂吗 我们全家的死期将至
Don't you see? Death is coming for our family.
你不相信我
You don't believe me.
对 我弄错了
No. Uh... um... Uh, I think I made a mistake.
我的梦也许没什么
I think it was probably just a dream.
不 等等 至少把笔记拿走
No, wait. At least take the book.
史黛芬妮
Stefani!
史黛芬妮 站住
Stefani! Stop!
抱歉 我不该来这里的
Look, I'm sorry. I shouldn't have come here.
这攸关我们的命脉
This book is a lifeline.
这会说明一切 能保护我们全家的安全
It will show you everything you need to know to keep our family safe.
你还是不相信我
You still don't believe me.
退后
Step back.
什么 为什么
What? Why?
眼见为实
Seeing is believing.
史黛 她的脸真的在你面前爆开...
Hey, Stef. Her face really explode right in front of you? Is that like--I'm...
艾瑞克 少烦她
Erik! Just leave her alone.
我嘴贱 史黛 我只是好奇
It's my bad, Stef. I'm just curious.
你还好吗
Hey. How are you holding up?
对不起 霍华德舅舅
I'm sorry, Uncle Howard.
你说得对 我不该去的
You were right about Iris. I never... I never should've went there.
亲爱的 没必要道歉
Honey, there's no need to apologize.
很遗憾你吓到了
I'm so sorry you had to go through that.
她临死前跟我说 我们全家的死期将至
She said something to me before she died. She said Death was coming for our family.
太离谱了 对吧
That's... That's crazy, right?
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
难以置信
I can't believe it.
我发电邮给她 没想到她会出现
I emailed her. I just didn't think she'd show up. I...
来吧
Come on.
妈来了?
Is that Mom?
对
Yeah.
达琳
Darlene!
-我晚点再来 -别傻了 下来
-I can come back. -Oh, don't be ridiculous. Come on.
下车 过来
Get down here. Come here.
你想她会一起来烤肉吗
Think she'll come to the barbecue?
史黛 等等
Stef. Hey, wait up.
她要去霍华德舅舅家 我就不去 你坐爸的车
If she's going to Uncle Howard's house, then I'm not. You can get a ride with Dad.
你不打算跟她说话?
You're not even going to talk to her?
别这样
Come on.
你不像我记得她多无情
You don't remember her like I do.
给她一次机会
Just give her a chance.
凭什么 她抛弃我们 现在才出现
Why? Charlie, she abandoned us, and now she rolls in here
过了这么多年 还装作没事
after all these years and wants to act like nothing happened?
也是 谁会这样 对吧
Yeah. Because who would do that, right?
等等 什么
Wait. What?
-没事 算了 -别走
-Nothing. Forget it. -No.
这是什么意思
No. What's that supposed to mean?
我打给你好几次都不接
I tried calling you so many times, and nothing.
茱莉亚也是碰壁 你们以前多要好 现在都不说话了
Same with Julia. You used to be best friends. You don't even talk anymore.
好 对不起 我...
Okay, I'm sorry, I...
我这几个月被恶梦搞到没心思
I've just been distracted the last couple of months because of this nightmare.
那之前呢 自从你离家就不理人
Okay, but what about before that? It's been like this ever since you left.
你很气妈 但你好不到哪里去
You're mad at Mom, but you haven't been around either.
我跟她不一样
I'm not like her!
好吗
Okay?
我没疯掉
I'm not crazy.
没错 你没疯掉
Yeah, you're right. You're not crazy.
你只是不在乎
You just don't care.
（给李奥教授  家有丧事...）
你很行嘛 别裂开
Now you got it. Watch out for splinters.
她来了
Hey, there she is!
过来 很高兴你来了
Come here. So glad you made it.
没想到你真的会来
You know, I didn't think you were actually going to come.
谢谢你邀请我
Thank you for inviting me.
别客气 进来
Of course. Come on in.
大家快过来
Hey, everybody! Come on! Come on over!
-我做了饼干 -太棒了
-I made cookies. -That's great!
-我能吃吗 -当然
-Can I try one? -Yes, of course.
这有加花生酱吗
Does this have peanut butter?
有
Yeah.
你想害死我弟吗
Are you trying to kill my brother?
-天啊 巴比有过敏 -对
-Oh, my God. Bobby's allergic. -Yeah.
我压根忘了 抱歉
I totally forgot. I'm so sorry.
总之你来了
You know, the most important thing is that you're here, so...
巴比酒保 开喝 大家喝个够
Bobby Bartender, drinks! Drinks all around!
家人 你没得选
Family. You don't get to pick the one you get...
但家人就要相亲相爱
just got to love the one that you got.
我们的母亲
Now, our mother...
她孤独终老
she lived alone until the day that she died.
她的离世提醒了我们大家
And her death should be a reminder to all of us
享受生活 共度相守的时光
to enjoy life and spend the time that we have together.
因为时光一去不复返
Because we're not going to get any back.
我爱你们
I love you guys.
干啦 干杯
Cheers to that! Cheers! Cheers!
后劲很强
This is strong.
你用什么调的
What did you put in there?
茱莉亚 茱莉亚
Julia? Oh, Jules!
你还好吗
Are you all right?
天啊 里面有虫
Oh, my God. There was a bug in there.
补充蛋白质
Extra protein.
打开了吗
You on?
-我行的 -省省吧
-I got it. -I don't think you've got it.
看我露一手
Oh, it's coming.
其实我刚接了救生工作
Actually, I'm starting a new lifeguarding job.
-太好了 -是啊
-That's great. -Yeah.
查理
Charlie!
上来这里
Get up here!
-艾瑞克 -妈 烤架好了
-Erik! -Ma, the grill's ready.
我能坐你旁边吗
Mind if I join you?
请坐 轻松点
Have a seat. Take a load off.
真好
There we go.
你把家里布置得真不错
It's quite the setup you've got here.
我希望孩子有个快乐童年
Well, I wanted the kids to have a happy childhood.
不像有些人没童年
Unlike some people I know.
你不是在说我们吧
You're not talking about us, are you?
-别误会 -我们的童年还真好
-Oh, no. -We had a great childhood.
看看我 我变得…棒呆了
I mean, look at me. I turned out... fabulous.
是啊
Yep.
霍华德
Howard.
-怎样 -拜托 这是什么
-What? -Come on. What is that?
看起来像是家里的钥匙
It looks like a house key to me.
-别扫兴 我们有空房 -我知道
-Come on. You know we've got the spare room. -I know.
总比流浪在停车场来得好
And it's got to be better than bouncing around trailer parks.
这是个馊主意
I don't think this is a good idea.
重新来过永远不嫌晚
It's never too late for a second chance.
对不起
I'm sorry.
他们没有我更好
They're better off without me.
快接电话
Pick up, pick up. Come on.
-等等 你在弹我或我在弹你 -你在弹我啦
-Okay, wait, you bounce me or I bounce you? -You're bouncing me, you're bouncing me.
（警告）
（前方危险）
爸 来秀一下你的后空翻
Hey, Dad! Come show us your backflip!
-什么 不要啦 -拜托 霍华德舅舅
-What? No, no, no. -Yeah, come on, Uncle Howard!
-来嘛 霍华德 -霍华德
-Come on, Howard! -Howard! Howard! Howard!
帮他一把
Help him out, help him out.
献丑了
Thank you.
-好耶 -行了
-Oh, yeah! -There you go.
好戏登场 照过来
All right. Here we go. Watch out.
等等 别动
Wait! Stop!
干得好 姑姑
Oh, nice catch, Aunt D.
-好 -开始了
-All right. -All right, here we go.
-好 爸 -咱们拼了
-Okay, Dad. -Let's do it.
-别靠近边缘 -加油 霍华德舅舅
-Stay away from that edge. -Come on, Uncle Howard.
-赞喔 海放大学生 -厉害
-There you go. Just like college. -Yep, nice.
-妈 看到没 -小心 霍华德
-Mom, you watch this? -Careful, Howard.
别抽那里啦
Not taking out of there.
作弊
That's cheating!
嘿 史黛芬妮
Hey, Stefani!
-你来了 -史黛芬妮
-You made it! -Stefani.
很高兴你决定过来
I'm glad you decided to come.
看大师出手了
Now watch the master.
全家到齐了
Now the whole family's here!
我很好 没事
I'm okay. I'm all right.
那就好
Whoa, good.
我没事
I'm okay.
没事的
It's okay.
没关系
It's all right.
往事已矣
The former things have passed away.
不再有哀号或痛苦
Neither shall there be mourning nor pain.
祂将抹去他们眼中的每滴眼泪
And he shall wipe away every tear from their eyes.
不再有死亡
And death shall be no more.
（JB发现有人逃过死劫）
（谁是JB?）
（爱莉丝  保罗  霍华德  达琳）
（艾瑞克  茱莉亚  巴比  史黛芬妮  查理）
这些是什么
What is all this stuff?
听好
Okay.
我在爱莉丝的笔记里找到这些文件
I found these papers in Iris' book.
有天景在场者的讣闻和报导
They are obituaries and articles for the people who were at the Sky View
就在爱莉丝出现预感的那晚
on the night that Iris had her premonition.
每个人的死法都很怪异和凄惨
Each one of these people went on to die in some weird and messed-up way.
不只如此 他们死的顺序跟爱莉丝的预感相同
And not only that, they all died in the same order as Iris' premonition.
那晚本来应该有几百人丧命 但爱莉丝阻止了灾难
Hundreds of people were supposed to die that night, but Iris stopped the disaster.
所以死神一个一个找上他们
So, Death came back for them one by one.
因为太多人幸存 死神花了好几年才找到所有人
Since there were so many survivors, it took years for Death to get to all of them.
最后死神还是找上爱莉丝
But eventually it got to Iris.
在预感中 她是最后死掉的人
I mean, she was the last to die in the premonition.
还有那个小男孩
It was her and the little boy.
但她做了周全准备
But she was prepared.
她独力阻挡死神几十年
She single-handedly held off Death for decades.
史黛芬妮 亲爱的 我认为现在不适合说这些
Stefani, sweetie, I don't think this is the appropriate time for this.
对 这些关我们什么事
Yeah, I mean, none of this even has anything to do with us, right?
-不对 -我们在这里干嘛
-No. -Why are we even here?
这跟我们大有关系
No, it has everything to do with us.
因为死神过了很久才除掉各个幸存者
I mean, because Death took so long to make its way through the survivors,
这些人后来有了家庭
these people went on to have families.
他们不应该有这些家人的
Families that they never should've had.
所以死神也带走他们
So Death took them, too.
你们没弄懂吗
I mean, don't you see this?
死神找上我们了 因为我们本来就不该存在
Death is coming for us because we were never supposed to exist.
好吧 那这里的每个人都在死神的暗杀名单上?
Okay, so, what, everybody in this room is on Death's "hit list"?
-巴比 别乱说 -我学她说的
-Bobby, stop. -That's what she's saying.
不是 爸和布兰达舅妈很安全 因为他们不是爱莉丝的血脉
No, no, no. Dad and Aunt Brenda are safe because they're not part of Iris' bloodline.
好
Okay,
照着这个模式...
following the pattern...
死神的目标是每一家从大到小
Death makes its way down each branch by age.
因为霍华德舅舅年纪最大 先从他的家人开始
So because Uncle Howard was the oldest, it'll start with his family first.
-所以艾瑞克是下一个 -去你的
-Meaning, Erik, you're next. -Go fuck yourself.
然后是茱莉亚 再来是巴比
Then it'll go for Julia, then Bobby.
接着是我们家 先是达琳 然后是我 再来是查理
Then it'll come for our branch, starting with Darlene, then me, then Charlie.
查理
Charlie.
你相信吗
You buying this?
我不确定
I don't know.
烂透了
This is so messed up.
你把我们老爸的死说成什么鬼阴谋论
I mean, you're turning our dad's death into some kind of fucked-up conspiracy theory.
-你是头壳坏掉吗 -不 不对
-What is wrong with you? -No, no, no.
-这不是阴谋论 -史黛 够了
-No, it's not a conspiracy theory. -Stef, enough.
-我们都会死 -别说了
-We're all going to die! -Stop!
我再也听不下去了
I can't listen to this for one more minute.
那疯女人的胡扯造成我们家太多痛苦
That crazy woman's nonsense has caused enough pain and suffering for this family.
等等 布兰达舅妈
Hang on. Aunt Brenda,
-听我说 -够啦 别管了
-please just listen. -For God's sake, leave it alone.
爱莉丝在笔记中提到有人骗了死神活下来
Okay, in Iris' book, she mentions somebody who cheated Death and survived.
史黛芬妮
Stefani.
-好啦 -艾瑞克 别走
-Come on. -Erik. No, wait.
-我很担心你 -闭嘴
-I'm worried about you. -Stop.
我来处理
Let me take care of this.
-来吧 巴比 走了 -布兰达
-Come on, Bobby. Let's go. -Brenda.
-布兰达 抱歉 我状况外 -不行 拜托
-Brenda, I'm sorry. I didn't know. -No, no, no. Please.
你相信我吧
You believe me, right?
-抱歉 -茱莉亚
-I'm sorry. -Julia.
听着 我爱你
Look, I love you.
但有时我很讨厌你
But sometimes I really hate you.
这一切好像说得通
I know how convincing all of this can be.
但不是真的
But it's not real.
你居然这样说
How can you say that?
爱莉丝都跟你说了
I know Iris taught you all of this.
别让我妈的念头毁掉你的人生
Don't let my mom's beliefs derail your life...
我的人生就被毁了
the same way they did mine.
感谢劝告 但我不缺妈妈了
Thank you so much for that advice, but I really don't need a mom anymore.
好 把嘴张大
All right, open wide.
很好
All right, good.
会痛喔 准备好了
-This is going to pinch, all right? You ready? -Mmm-hmm.
5 4 3
Five, four, three...
2 1
...two, one.
好极了
Good job.
我准备去夜店 你要关门
Ready to hit the club. Need you to lock up.
别碰我的酒
And don't touch any of my liquor.
不行 你没说要关门
No, no, you didn't say anything about locking up.
-随便 -你又没说要关门 老兄
-Yeah, yeah, yeah. -You didn't say shit about closing, dude!
哭死吧你
Yeah, cry me a river.
希望你下地狱
I hope you burn in hell!
信不信有这种鸟事
Do you believe that shit?
我爸刚死 我来帮那烂人的忙 他竟然还要我关门
My old man just died. I come in as a favor to that asshole, and now he wants me to lock up.
知道这算什么吗
You know what that is?
知道吗 不管别人死活
You know what that is? It's inconsiderate.
行啦 你好了
Anyway, you're all done.
谢谢
Thank you.
记得 五星评价 按赞和订阅喔
Of course. Hey, five-star review, yeah? Like and subscribe and all the... things.
（营业中）
（艾瑞克刺青歌单）
（万用消毒剂）
（史黛芬妮：你还好吗 ）
（滚开）
（表妹  去睡觉）
（艾瑞克疗伤歌单）
♪ 我不会忘记这个夜晚 ♪
♪ 以及你离去时的面庞 ♪
♪ 也许这就是故事发展的方式 ♪
♪ 现在一切变得公平 现在我只想让你知道 ♪
♪ 一些你该知道的事 ♪
♪ 我活不下去 ♪
♪ 如果生命中失去了你 ♪
♪ 我再也无法付出 ♪
♪ 我活不下去 ♪
♪ 如果生命中失去了你 ♪
♪ 我再也无法付出 ♪
（爸）
♪ 我无法忘记今晚 ♪
♪ 当你离去时的脸庞 ♪
♪ 但我想那就是故事的结局 ♪
♪  你一直保持着笑容 但眼里却流露着哀伤 ♪
可恶
Oh, God damn it.
♪ 没错 那是哀伤 ♪
♪ 我活不下去 ♪
♪ 如果生命中失去了你 ♪
搞什么鬼
What the fuck?
♪ 我再也无法付出 ♪
够了
Come on.
快点
好了
Okay, okay.
快点
Okay, come on.
该死
Shit!
（危险勿入  高电压）
查理 快醒醒
Charlie, wake up. Charlie, wake...
查理 醒醒 我整晚打给艾瑞克
Charlie, wake up! I've been trying to call Erik all night.
他都没接 他人在哪 我很担心
He's not answering me. I don't know where he is. I'm worried.
他一定没事的
I'm sure he's fine.
你有他的消息吗
Well, have you heard from him?
我要过去看看他
I'm going over there. I need to check on him.
你也要一起去 查理
And you're coming, too, Charlie!
一直转到语音信箱
It keeps going to voicemail.
是他吗
Is that him?
我朋友说昨晚刺青店被烧毁
My friend just said the tattoo parlor burned down last night.
什么
What?
史黛 史黛
Stef, Stef, Stef!
好痛 想撞死我吗
Ow! You trying to kill me?
艾瑞克
Erik?
果不其然 是你
Oh, yeah, no, of course it's you.
哥
Dude!
听说有火灾 我们以为你死了
We heard about the fire. We thought you were dead.
我没事
I'm fine.
天啊 你还好吧 我很担心你
Oh, my God. Are you okay? I was so worried about you.
消防员说我超幸运 还好我穿了皮夹克
Yeah. The firefighters said I was lucky as fuck that I was wearing that leather jacket.
连烧伤都没有
Barely got burned.
只是毁了我最爱的夹克
Ruined my favorite jacket though.
-这是怎样 -看好了
-What is this? -Oh, yeah, check it out.
爱的烙印
I got branded.
很屌吧
It's sick, right?
你们喜欢吗
You like it?
你说你睡着了
You said you were asleep.
你死缠烂打狂呼 我还能怎样
You were blowing up my phone like a goddamn stalker. What did you want me to do?
我不懂 你早该死了
No, I don't get it. You should be dead.
最好是
Right. Yeah, yeah.
搞不好…
Or, you know, maybe...
也许死神根本不会找上我们家
Maybe Death's not actually coming for our family.
不然就太夸张了
Because that would be fucking crazy.
老天 该死
Jesus! Shit!
或许我就是死不了
Or maybe I'm invincible.
艾瑞克 艾瑞克
Erik. Erik!
-干嘛 -艾瑞克 等等 先别走
-Yeah? -Erik, wait. Stop, just wait, okay?
就算死神昨晚没杀你 也不一定安全
Just because Death didn't kill you last night, doesn't mean that you're safe.
别靠近剪枝机
Stay away from that tree trimmer!
它会自己动吗 会吗
Is it going to move on its own, Stef? Is that what it's going to do?
它可能会掉下来
It could fall.
别靠近这些小孩
And stay away from these kids.
我宁愿冒险
I'll take my chances.
史黛 两个玩足球的小鬼能怎么杀他
Stef, how's a couple kids with a soccer ball going to kill him?
很难说
I mean, I don't know.
剪枝机可能会掉下来 打到吹叶机男
The trimmer could fall and hit the leaf blower guy, which causes him to...
小孩眼睛被吹到 然后把球踢到他脸上
blow stuff into the kids' eyes and then kick the ball into his face.
足球踢到我脸上?
Soccer ball to my face?
听起来很致命
That does sound deadly.
我应该更小心的
I should be more careful.
-嗨 -是你
-Hey! -What's up?
你怎么了
What happened to you?
被死神烤焦了 还用说
Charbroiled by Death, apparently.
-看起来很惨 -没事啦
-Kiki, that looks really bad. -Yeah, it's fine.
等等 让我看
No, wait. Let me see that.
-艾瑞克 离卡车远一点 -住手
-Erik, just stay away from the truck. -Stop.
-卡车又怎样 -别过去
-Oh, what, this truck? -Stop!
-我的天 -拜托
-Oh, my God. -Please.
-这辆卡车 -好歹听我说
-This truck right here? -Please just listen to me for one...
-这辆卡车好正点 -拜托住手 别碰
-But it's such a beautiful truck. -Please. Stop, stop. Don't touch...
艾瑞克 离开 住手
Erik, get away! Stop!
-这样你喜欢吗 -你能不能…
-You like that? -Can you just...
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
艾瑞克又在挑衅死神 会怎样
Oh, Erik's tempting Death again. What's going to happen?
-别闹了 -会发生什么事
-Stop doing that! -What is going to happen?
-根本没怎样 -拜托
-Nothing at all. -Please, just...
-打脸你了 -我只是想帮你
-How about that? -Look, I'm just trying to help you.
-好了 -认真就输了
-Okay. -Try less.
说实话 我们受够你的鬼扯了
Yeah. Honestly, we are so done with your garbage.
-你能不能… -我说了1,500次了
-Can you please---Okay, for the 1,500th time,
没人鸟你那蠢死亡诅咒
no one gives a shit about your stupid little Death curse, okay?
识相点 少烦我们 因为死神不会找上我们家的
So take a hint and leave us alone because Death's not coming for our family!
茱莉亚
Julia!
惨了
Shit.
-茱莉亚 -茱莉亚
-Julia! -Julia!
停车 停车
Stop the truck! Stop the truck!
-停车 -喂
-Stop the truck! -Hey! Hey!
-我妹妹在垃圾车里 -还不停车
-Stop the fucking truck! -My sister's in the garbage!
救命
Help!
-茱莉亚 -史黛
-Julia? -Stef!
把手给我
Give me your hand!
我抓住你了
I got you!
别担心 你不是下一个
Don't worry, you're not next!
-救命 -停车
-Help! -Hey, stop! Stop!
-停车 -停车
-Stop! -Stop!
-Stop! Stop! -Stop!
-我妹妹在后面 -史黛
-Stef! -My sister's in the back!
-很遗憾 女儿 -爸
-I'm so sorry, sweetie. -Dad.
我们该相信你的 史黛
We should've believed you, Stef.
可惜我…
No, I, uh...
我搞错顺序 茱莉亚死掉是我的错
I screwed up the order, and now Julia's dead and it's my fault.
大家听着 这些事故很创伤又可怕
Guys, look. What happened was traumatic and awful.
-不是谁的错 -马帝 别说了
-It's not anybody's fault. -Marty, please don't.
是我的错
It's my fault.
妈 不是你的错
Mom, it's not your fault.
是我的错
It is my fault.
史黛芬妮 你有所不知才弄错顺序
Stefani, you were only wrong about the order because there is something you didn't know.
艾瑞克不是霍华德的亲生儿子
Erik isn't Howard's biological son.
什么 你在说什么
I'm sorry. What are you talking about?
史黛芬妮 我本来不相信才瞒着你
And, Stefani, I didn't believe you, so I didn't say anything to you,
结果我女儿死了
and now my little girl is dead.
我不懂 你有外遇?
I don't understand. What, you had an affair?
我和你爸当时感情不太好
Your father and I were having such a hard time...
但后来好转 因为我怀了你
but it was good because I got you.
-我生下你 -谁是我的生父
-I got you out of it. -Who's my real dad then? Who's my real dad?
不重要 因为霍华德非常爱你
It doesn't matter because Howard loved you so, so much.
是谁
Who is it?
我的生父是谁
Who's my real dad?
杰瑞·芬伯里
Jerry Fenbury.
杰瑞·芬伯里?
Jerry Fenbury?
对
Yes.
要命
Oh, shit.
-不会吧 他妈的居然是杰瑞·芬伯里? -艾瑞克
-No, no, no! Jerry fucking Fenbury? -Erik.
你不懂我们吃了多少苦
You don't know what we were going through.
天啊 怪不得他常找我玩接球
Oh, God! What, is this why he always wanted to play catch?
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
好吧
Okay.
这表示如果顺序正确...
All right, so, that means that, if it's going in the right order, that...
我是下一个 对吧
I'm next, right?
你要帮我 史黛
You got to help me, Stef.
巴比 我无能为力
Bobby, I don't... I don't think that I can.
我没把握
I mean, I thought I did, but I don't know--
你行的
No. But you can.
你精准预测到未来的事
I mean, you predicted exactly what was going to happen.
你只是弄错顺序 因为你缺乏资讯
You just got the order wrong because you didn't have all the information.
-查理 -"预测"是什么意思
-Charlie. -What do you mean "predicted"?
她都看到了
She saw everything.
剪枝机 吹叶机 足球
The trimmer, the blower, the soccer ball. Like...
这就像拼图碎片 她只要拼凑起来
It was like there were pieces to a puzzle. She just had to put them together.
-懂吗 -真的吗
-You know what I mean? -Is that true?
达琳 拜托 别火上添油
Darlene, please. Do not encourage this.
马帝
Marty.
爱莉丝的笔记里写得一清二楚
I mean... I mean, it's everything in Iris' book,
像是方程式 是数学
it's... It's like an equation. It's math.
史黛芬妮 只要你能看出一切的组合 我们或许就有机会
Stefani, if you can see how all of this fits together, we might have a chance.
够了 别说了
Stop. Just stop.
你走人时把整个家毁了 但我们没有你也过得很好
You devastated this family when you walked out. But we've been okay without you.
求你别再伤害我们的孩子
I'm begging you not to traumatize our kids anymore.
这次是真的
It's real this time.
我去散个步
I'm going for a walk.
我要透透气
I need some air.
我能理解…
I can appreciate that...
我们之后少不了家庭谘商
our family is clearly going to need some counseling in the future,
但先专注在我们都会死的事实吧
but can we focus on the fact that we're all about to die, right?
史黛
I mean, Stef,
你不是说爱莉丝…
didn't you say that... that Iris...
知道有人骗过死神吗
knew someone that cheated death or something?
对
Yeah, uh...
在这里有写
In here, somewhere.
上面说...
It says... that, uh...
在这里 "JB发现有人逃过死劫"
Right here. "JB found someone who survived."
但没说JB是谁
But it doesn't say anything about who this JB was or--
等一下 我听过这个名字
Wait a minute. I know that name.
我妈以前常写信给我
My mom used to write me letters,
她有时会提到她朋友JB在医院工作
and she sometimes would talk about a friend of hers named JB who worked at a hospital.
医院
Hospital.
什么河流医院
Something, uh... Something River Hospital. Uh...
深河 和平河医院 清河
Deep River. Uh... Peace River Hospital. Uh, Clear River...
-希望河 -没错
-Hope River? -That's it!
不远 一小时车程
Shit, it's like an hour away.
我要去找他 亲自跟他谈
I'm going. I'm going to go find him and talk to him myself.
我跟你去
Well, I'm coming with you.
-我也是 -好 我们走
-Me, too. -Okay. Yeah, yeah, let's go.
巴比
Bobby, uh...
怎样
What?
你留下来陪你妈比较安全
You need to stay here with your mom. It's safer.
管他的 有没有搞错 我才不要落单呢
Yeah, fuck that. Are you kidding me? I'm not staying here by myself.
你在路上太危险 不行
Well, it's too dangerous on the road for you. You can't.
我有读外婆的死亡笔记 好吗
No, I read Gammy's Death Book, okay? All right?
有超多人死在家里
I mean, there's, like, a thousand house-related deaths in that thing, man.
跌下楼梯 摔下马桶之类的
You trip down the stairs, fall... down a toilet or something.
太多了 免谈 我才不要留下来
I don't know, but I'm not... I'm not... No way. I'm not staying here.
-等等 -行了
-Hang on, hang on. -Hey, okay.
-好 -太快了
-Okay. -Too fast.
-好 慢慢来 -我去开车
-Okay, okay. We'll go slow. We'll go slow. -I'm going to go open up the truck.
-查理 检查后面 -好
-Charlie, check the back. -Got it.
小心 有时台阶很滑
Be careful. The step's slippery sometimes.
喂
Oi!
谁有去搜坚果吗
Any of you fuckers do a nut check?
你说什么
Excuse me?
你几天前用花生酱做了饼干
You made cookies in that thing with peanut butter in them just a few days ago.
这可怜鬼连碰到一颗坚果
This poor bastard so much as even touches a nut,
喉咙都会卡死
his throat is going to close up tighter than...
别装傻 花生酱呢
You understand. Where's the peanut butter?
-水槽上方的柜子 -谢谢
-Cabinet above the sink. -Thank you.
抱歉 巴比 我只是…
I'm so sorry, Bobby. I just...
好吧
Yeah.
搞定
Hey. Okay.
安全了
All clear.
谢谢 你真是好兄弟 艾瑞克
Thank you. You're a good brother, Erik.
-搜你的坚果 -什么
-Nut check. -What?
笨蛋
Stupid.
你也帮帮忙
It was good. I get it.
走吧 上来
Let's go. Come on.
真是痛死了
It's only going to get worse.
该死 等等 我陪你去 兄弟
God damn it. Wait! I'm coming with you, bro.
总得有人保护你
Someone's got to protect you.
爸又打来了
Dad's calling. Again.
跟他说我们和妈去兜风
Tell him we just went for a ride with Mom.
他才不会信
He's not going to believe that.
起码能争取一些时间
At least it'll buy us some time.
好吧
All right.
死神没逮到我们 倒是被你爸骂死
If Death doesn't get us, your dad will.
我一直放着随时能看
I always keep them where I can see them.
你明明能看本人的
I mean, you could've just had the real thing,
算了 不是每个人都想当妈
but it's okay, not everyone wants to be a mom.
你这样认为?
Is that what you think?
我不想当你妈
That I didn't want to be your mom?
听着 把我养大的女人教我到处留意死神
Look, I was raised by a woman who taught me to see Death everywhere.
我以为我能放下 但你和你弟出生时
I thought I could put it behind me, but then when I had you and your brother,
我满脑子想着你和查理的上百种死法
all I could see were a hundred different ways that you and Charlie could die.
我不让你们出门
I didn't want you to leave the house.
无缘无故对你们发脾气
I would freak out on you guys over nothing.
有一天我看着你的脸
One day, I looked at your face
我看到像我童年时那个受惊的小女孩
and I saw the same scared little girl that I was, growing up,
我觉得我留下会毁了你一生
and I knew that if I stayed, I was going to ruin your life.
我不确定我的抉择对不对
I have no idea if I did the right thing.
但现在我会挺你
But I'm here for you now.
没事的
It's okay.
我就在你后面
I'm right behind you.
看吧 老弟 有我们在
Hey. Now you see, buddy. We got you.
柜台在这边
The front desk is this way.
（尸体解剖中）
嗨 我们想找JB
Hi. Uh... we're looking for JB.
你是谁
And who are you?
柜台说他在这里 是你吗
The front desk told us we could find him down here. Is that you?
是我
That would be me.
威廉·约翰·布鲁沃斯 我朋友都叫我JB
William John Bludworth. But my friends call me JB.
我一直在等你 史黛芬妮
I've been waiting for you, Stefani.
查理 达琳
Charlie, Darlene.
没有霍华德和茱莉亚
But no Howard, no Julia.
所以你们下一个是谁
So, which one of you is next?
嗨
Hi.
很遗憾爱莉丝走了
I was sorry to hear about Iris.
她是很特别的人
She was a special woman.
你怎么认识她的
How did you know her?
她救了我一命
She saved my life.
什么时候
When?
在天景
At the Sky View.
我妈那晚带我去上班
My mother brought me with her to work that night.
JB宝贝 我说过我上台时你要待在后面
JB, honey, I told you, you got to stay back there while I'm on stage.
我本来不该在场 除非注定一死
I wasn't supposed to be there, except, of course, to die.
♪ 你就是会让我想喊叫 踢起脚跟 喊叫 ♪
停止演奏
Stop playing!
大家快离开舞池
Everyone needs to get off the dance floor!
玻璃快碎了 大家快离开
The glass is about to break. Everyone needs to get off now!
等等 不要
Wait! No!
爱莉丝
Iris!
你是那个最后死掉的小男孩
You were the last to die. You were the little boy.
正解
Correct.
所以一直以来
So, all that time, she wasn't...
她不只在保护家人 也在保护你
She wasn't just protecting our family, she was protecting you, too.
几年后她找到我
Years later, she tracked me down.
教我看清真相
Helped me see the truth.
我们交换意见 我帮她盖了小屋
We traded ideas. I helped her fortify her cabin.
我们成了朋友
We became friends.
我还帮她安排最好的治疗
I even helped her get the best medical care I could,
因为她罹癌
considering her condition.
爱莉丝说你发现有人阻止死神活下来
Iris said that you found somebody who stopped Death and survived.
是的
Yes.
我们要怎么做
Uh, and how do we do that?
只有两种方法
There are only two ways.
杀人或死亡
By killing or by dying.
杀人就能得到对方的余命
If you take a life, you get the time that person had left.
什么 我才不要杀人
What? No! I'm not going to kill someone.
先听他说完
Maybe we should let the guy finish.
要真正打破循环 就要死过一次
And to truly break the cycle, you have to die.
什么意思
What... What does that mean?
很久以前 有个叫做金柏莉·柯曼的年轻女子
A long time ago, a young woman named Kimberly Corman
发现自己在死神名单上 跟你们一样
found herself on Death's list. Just like you.
最后轮到她时 她死了
And when her turn finally came, she died.
心电图静止
Flatlined.
医生拼命救回她 就打破了宿命
But her doctor managed to bring her back, and that broke the chain.
-那就这么办 -你在说什么
-All right then, we'll do that. -What are you talking about?
爱莉丝为什么不试试
Uh... why didn't Iris try that?
这是一步险棋
It's risky.
敢跟死神作对却输了
And if you fuck with Death and lose,
情况会变得更糟
things can get very messy.
等一下 等等
Wait. Hang on, hang on. Okay, wait. No.
一定有别的办法 拜托你帮帮我们
There has to be another way. Please, you have to help us.
多年来大家都来向我求救
For years, people have been coming to me for advice.
我很累 我受够了
Well, I'm tired. I'm done with all that.
现在我跟爱莉丝一样生病 这次逃不了
And now I'm sick, just like Iris. There's no running this time.
残酷的事实 你们都会死
The fact is, you're all going to die.
之后我也会死
And after that, I will, too.
既然我的老朋友走了 我会隐退
Now that my old friend is gone, I'm retiring.
-所以你要丢下我们 -等等
-So, what, you're just gonna leave us here? -Wait, wait, wait!
-老兄 我们需要你帮忙 -你要去哪
-Dude, we need your help. -Where are you going?
我想享受最后的时光
I intend to enjoy the time I have left.
我建议你们学学我
And I suggest that you do the same.
生命很宝贵
Life is precious.
充分享受每一刻
Enjoy every single second.
你永远猜不到死期
You never know when.
祝好运
Good luck.
真是好棒
Well, that's fantastic.
-不对 -巴比
-No. No, that... -Bobby.
不可能 找找看
That can't be it. No. No, there...
这里一定藏着什么转机
There has to be something here. There has to be another answer.
史黛 他给我们答案了
Stef. Stef. Stef, he gave us an answer.
巴比非死不可
Bobby's got to die.
艾瑞克
Erik!
你疯了吗 我们才不会杀巴比
Are you fucking insane? We're not killing Bobby!
只有我听懂他的话吗
Am I the only guy that just listened to that dude?
只有一个办法
There's only one way.
把巴比弄死 再救活他 你们就不在死神名单上
We kill Bobby, we resuscitate him, and then, boom, you're all off Death's list.
-恭喜 -一定有别的办法
-Congratulations. -There has to be something else, right?
一定有其他解决办法吧 史黛
I mean, there has to be another solution, right, Stef?
没有
No.
我们无计可施 没辙了
No, there's nothing else we can do, okay? It's over.
-听好 -史黛芬妮 听我说
-Hey. -Stefani, listen to me.
这次你要相信我 她要放弃你 但我不会
You got to trust me on this one, okay? She's giving up on you, I'm not going to.
爱莉丝想办法阻挡死神几十年
Look, Iris found a way to hold Death off for decades.
-我们也行的 -我相信那家伙
-So will we. -I trust that guy.
你相信那家伙?
You trust that guy?
他讲话头头是道 你和我都信了吧
He was awfully charismatic, and you know that as well as I do.
艾瑞克和巴比不见了
Erik and Bobby are gone.
不好了
Shit. Shit!
这不是好点子
I don't think I like this.
别慌 记住我们在医院 到处是医生
Hey, dude, we're in a hospital, remember? There's doctors everywhere.
弄死你 再让你复活 大家都安全 我们成了英雄
We kill you, they bring you back, everybody's safe, we're heroes.
靠 这是哪门子保护我安全啊
Dude, that is literally the opposite of keeping me safe.
还有别的选择吗
What's the alternative, huh?
你想杀人夺走对方的余命吗
You want to kill someone, take the time they have left?
怎么做 你哪知道别人还能活几年
How? How do you even know how many years they have?
-不行 -不 这可不行
-No. No. -No. Not good with that.
-可是… -不行
-Well, I mean... -No.
-想都别想 -太缺德了
-No, of course not. -We wouldn't do that.
-打死不行 -别碰宝宝
-No, we would never. -Don't touch those babies.
听着 重点是...
Look, bottom line...
死而复生是最上策
flatlining is your best option.
你没什么好损失的?
What do you have to lose?
-好吧 -好吧
-Okay. -Okay.
那我们要怎么做
All right, how would we even do that?
听好 我有个主意
See, I've got an idea.
但有点疯狂
But it's a little nuts.
（无盐花生）
你的过敏很致命吧
Your allergy is deadly, right?
对
Yeah.
正好
Well...
哥 等等
Hey, dude, wait.
听着 就算要死 我也不要死于…
No, look, all right? If I'm going out, it's not going to be on those...
食之无味的玩意
what, unsalted bitches, all right?
给我那个
Give me those.
（花生酱杯  加量坚果）
选得好
Nice choice.
（警告  请勿摇晃或倾斜）
开什么玩笑 快点
Oh, you got to be kidding me. Come on!
-嘿 -有够蠢
-Hey. -Stupid!
-别气 -快点
-All right. -Come on!
也许这是征兆 我们能…
You know, maybe this is a sign, so we can just...
好了 也许我们该走了
Okay. Hey, dude, maybe we can just bail now.
我才不会半途而废
No, I'm not giving up.
-搞什么 -你能帮忙吗
-What the hell? -Can you help?
不要紧 我们是员工
It's all right. We work here.
维修工 没事 戴上耳机
Maintenance. It's fine. Put your headphones back on.
靠 快倒了 机器会倒
Dude, it's going to fall. It's going to fall.
-天啊 快倒了 -你抬高了
-Oh, my! It's falling! -Did you get it up?
我撑不住 快倒了
I can't hold it! It's going to fall!
轻轻松松
Easy work.
接着呢
Now what?
跟我来
Come with me. Come with me.
什么
What?
等着 我去找个东西
Hey, hang here. I got to get something.
-别乱跑 -你是说…
-Don't move. -What are you talk...
（系统启动）
好 别乱跑
Okay. Don't move.
没事 没关系
No, that's... that's cool.
我找过洗手间 他们不在车上
I searched the bathrooms. They weren't in the RV?
不在 艾瑞克想弄死巴比 会在哪
No. Look, if Erik was trying to kill Bobby, where would they be?
说不准 但在医院有无数死法
I don't know, but there's a million ways to die in a hospital.
请问有事吗
Can I help you? Excuse me.
没事 我只是来看我奶奶
No, just here to see my nana.
今天的天气真好
Lovely day today.
你还能活很久吗
Got much time left?
应该吧
I think so.
请务必移除所有金属物品和装置
Be sure to remove all metallic belongings and devices that could interact
以避免与磁振造影强力磁铁互动
with the MRI's powerful magnet.
-查理打电话来了 -给我
-Hey, uh, dude, Here, man, give me that. -Charlie's trying to call..
过来 坐下 快坐
Here, come on. Sit down. Sit, sit, sit.
搞什么 我才不要坐轮椅
What the hell? No, I'm not sitting in that.
我有个好主意
Well, I've got a great idea.
走廊那边有急诊室 你一死掉
Okay, there's an ER down the hall. So, as soon as you flatline, boom.
我会把你推过去 他们就能把你救回
I'm going to wheel your ass down there and they're going to bring you right back.
你的肾上腺素呢
Hey, where's your EpiPen?
-在这里 -给我
-It's right here. -Give it to me.
干嘛
Why?
-怎么回事 -给我
-What is that? -Dude, give it. Give it.
听着 重点是你要死成
Listen, the whole idea is you have to die.
记住这会让你活命 坐着
Remember, this keeps you alive. Now sit.
-我们要赶快 动作快 -好吧
-Dude, we need to hurry. Come on. Go. -All right, all right.
吃吧
All right, eat up.
老哥
Hey, man, um...
这计划很棒 但如果不成功
The plan's great, but, you know, if it doesn't work out...
一定会成功的 巴比
It's going to work, Bobby.
好
Yeah.
好 但以防万一 我真的死掉...
Yeah, but, you know, just in case, and I die for real...
你能不能…
will you just, um...
你能照顾帕哥吗
Will you look after Paco?
当然 我会照顾的
Yeah, yeah, of course I'll look after--Dude, I'm just saying,
不唬人 乌龟能活到一百岁
I mean, turtles live to be, like, 100 years old,
-一言为定喔 -看着我
-and it's a lifetime commitment. -Look at me. Look at me.
兄弟 我不要照顾帕哥 因为你不会有事
Brother, I'm not going to take care of Paco because you are going to be okay.
我和你要为大家解决问题
Me and you, we are going to fix things for everyone right now.
看着我
Look at me.
我保证不会让你死
I promise you, I'm not going to let you die.
照理说我会让你死 但也会救活你
Technically, I'm going to let you die, but I'm going to bring you back.
-这不好笑 -我只是在逗你
-Dude, it's not funny. -I'm just fucking with you.
别泄气
Come on.
你行的
You got this.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
怎样
What?
超好吃的
That's really good.
废话 除了好吃 你有什么感觉
It's very good, I know. So, what, other than good, what are you feeling?
没感觉
Nothing.
你在开玩笑吧 你是说你不再过敏了?
You got to be kidding me. What, are you telling me you're not allergic anymore?
-我不知道 -也太刚好了
-I don't know, man. -This is perfect, isn't it?
也许我长大就好了
Maybe I grew out of it.
长大就好了? 操蛋
What, grew out of it? Fuck!
我完全没有备用计划
You know, I don't have a plan B exactly.
你发作了
Hey, dude. Hey, hey, you're doing it.
巴比 你发作了
Bobby, you're doing it.
我会陪着你
Hey, I'm here with you.
I'm here with you.
我不能给你 好吗
Hey, hey. I can't give you that, okay?
巴比 巴比
Bobby, Bobby. Hey.
别慌
Hey!
拜托
Please.
巴比 这在计划内 冷静点
Bobby, this is all part of the plan. Just calm down.
（需要手动操作）
巴比 坐上轮椅
Bobby, in the wheelchair.
再打给他们
Try calling them again.
别无他法了...
This is the only way we can do...
（研究功率等级  开启）
操
Fuck!
（请勿超过5兆  功率等级警告）
（磁力  最大等级）
我的天 你还好吗
Oh, my God. Are you okay?
还好
Yeah.
艾瑞克跟爱莉丝没有血缘 为什么会死
Why is Erik dead if he's not related to Iris?
敢跟死神作对 情况会变得更糟
When you fuck with Death, things get messy.
我们要离开这里
We have to get out of here.
这里不安全
It's not safe.
去哪
And go where?
哪都不安全
Nowhere is safe.
除了爱莉丝的小屋
Except Iris' cabin.
她在那里存活几十年
She was able to survive there for decades.
对 然后她的脸爆掉
Yeah, and then she got her face blown off.
她死掉是因为她离开小屋
She only died because she left the cabin.
外面很危险 但里面是最安全的地方
Outside is dangerous, but inside is the safest place that there is.
你说得对
You're right.
我们只有去那里才有优势
It's the only place where we have any advantage.
所以我们一辈子都要关在小屋里?
So we just lock ourselves in a cabin forever?
不是你
Not you.
是我
Me.
妈 别走 你才刚回来
Mom, you can't leave. We just got you back.
一定要有人住进小屋 那就是我
If anybody's going to live in that cabin, it's me.
只要我还活着 死神就不会碰你们
And as long as I am alive, Death can't touch you.
-妈 -交给我吧
-Mom. -Let me do this.
他不会让你一个人安全抵达
He'll never let you get there on your own.
但我能看见他出现
But I can see him coming.
我们要一起去
We have to do this together.
好吧
Okay.
好
走吧
Let's go.
好了
Yep.
Okay.
小心
Watch out!
-应该由你开车 -对
-You should drive. -Yeah.
该死
Holy shit.
看看这个地方
Look at this place.
过不了大门的
It's going to be impossible to get through that gate.
他打算行动了
He's about to make a move.
我不确定是怎样
I don't know what it is.
我们要马上带你进去
We need to get you inside now.
好
Okay.
等等 什么
Wait. Wait, what?
上
Go!
史黛
Stef!
-史黛  -我靠
-Stef! -Shit!
好 我们进去
Okay. Let's get inside.
好
Okay.
-糟糕  -什么
-Shit. -What?
-我来帮忙 -不必 别等我 快进去
-I can help. -No, no. Don't wait for me. Just get inside.
-史黛 -你进去 我就会安全 快去
-Stef. -If you get inside, I'll be safe. Go.
好 快来
Okay. Come on.
妈
Mom.
趴下
Get down!
妈 妈
Mom? Mom!
等等
Wait.
好了
Okay, okay.
妈 天啊
Mom? Oh, my God.
别担心我 去救你姐
Don't worry about me. Go save your sister.
我会活着 只要我…
I'm going to stay alive as long as I--
史黛
Stef!
不要
No! No!
我的天 你还好吗
Oh, my God. Are you okay?
还好
Yeah.
深呼吸 深呼吸
Just breathe. Breathe. Breathe.
怎么会
How?
查理 发生什么事
Charlie. What happened?
你没事了
You're okay.
你死了 我把你救回来了
You died and I brought you back.
你把我救回来了
You brought me back.
我们安全了
We're safe now.
妈呢
Mom?
不要
No. No.
她救了我们
She saved us.
我们回家吧
Let's go home.
我准备好了
All right, I'm ready.
帅哥出场
Well, there he is.
不错啊 查理
Wow. Okay, Charlie.
好了 转一圈
All right. Give us a spin.
你看起来真潇洒
You look really good.
我有很棒的造型师
I have a great stylist.
快点 我们要迟到了
Come on, we're going to be late.
珍妮在哪
Where's Jenny?
她应该还在里面准备
I think she's still inside getting ready.
来 我调整一下
Here, let me fix this.
我很高兴能陪你来
I'm really happy I could be here for this.
我也是
Me, too.
你还好吗
You okay?
还好
Yeah.
-嗨 -你好
-Hi. -Hello.
能给我一块饼干吗
Could I have one cookie, please?
查理
Charlie.
-很帅喔 -谢谢 先生
-Looking sharp. -Thank you, sir.
史黛 这位是珍妮的父亲雷迪克医生
Stef, I want you to meet Jenny's dad, Dr. Reddick.
-嗨 幸会 -嗨
-Hey. Nice to meet you. -Hi.
你也是
You, too.
我们很喜欢查理
We just adore Charlie.
我还知道他救人一命
And I understand he's quite the lifesaver.
你听说了 他让我起死回生
Oh, yeah. You heard about that. He brought me back from the dead.
不好说
Yeah.
-什么 -严格来说你没有死
-What? -Well, technically, you weren't dead.
什么
What?
如果你昏迷 查理让你恢复呼吸
Well, I mean, if you were unconscious, and Charlie got you breathing again,
你的心脏就没有停
then your heart didn't stop.
你还是很了不起 查理
But regardless, way to go, Charlie.
-所以她不算死过 -没错
-So she wasn't dead? -Exactly.
她很幸运查理在场
She was lucky Charlie was there.
对 上天自有安排
Yep. Everything happens for a reason.
珍妮
Jenny!
宝贝 你看起来美极了
Sweetie, you look like a million bucks.
史黛
Stef.
快跑
Run!
天啊 就差一点
Oh, my God, that was close.
-你没事吧  -没事
-Are you okay? -Yeah.
死神来了6：血脉诅咒
（1968年  天景塔关闭维修）
（无人伤亡  结构需翻新）
（水上乐园灾难  青少年从塔上滑落）
（一家人在工业事故中惨死）
（惨绝人寰的公路意外）
（电锯夺走当地男子性命  微波炉爆炸导致女子死亡）
（父母离世两天后双胞胎死亡  令人震惊的双重悲剧）
（老妇被风向仪刺穿）
（公寓瓦斯外泄  大楼夺命）
（列车出轨悲剧）
谨以本片纪念托尼·托德